SHANNA LUCERO

Full Stack Web Developer

CONTACT

■ shannaCodes@icloud.com

② Camarillo, CA, USA

linkedin.com/in/shannalucero

shannaCodes.netlify.app

EDUCATION

Nucamp Coding Bootcamp

May 2023 - October 2023 Certificate in Full Stack Web & Mobile App Development

Cal State Dominguez Hills

M.S. Occupational Therapy

Cal State Long Beach

B.S. Business Administration,
Management Information Systems

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- MongoDB
- Expres
- React
- Node
- SQL
- Github
- JIRA
- AGILE Scrum Methodology
- End User Training
- Technical Documentation

PROFILE

Mission-driven full stack web developer with 10+ years of previous experience in the healthcare industry as a clinician, leader, and mentor. I aim to solve problems and enjoy the process. My ideal role will allow me to collaborate within a forward-thinking team, contribute to exciting projects, and grow within a supportive environment.

PROJECTS

Hand Exercise App

Full stack CRUD app aimed for for rehab professionals to create and share custom home exercise programs

- Skills: React, RESTFUL APIs, JSON Web Tokens, User Authentication, JSX, HTML, CSS, Express, Node, & MongoDB
- Github: github.com/shannacodes/handtherapy-ex
- Live Page: hand-ex.web.app/

Pick For Me App

A fun front end app intended to solve the dilemma of indecisive people and/or couples for figuring out "What to eat?"

- Skills: React, RESTFUL APIs, HTML, CSS, Express, Node, & MongoDB
- Github: github.com/shannacodes/pick-what-to-eat
- Live Page: pick-4-me.netlify.app/

Rolling Pin Donuts

Revamped a popular local donut shop's web presence to modern, user-friendly and responsive experience

- Skills: Bootstrap, Javascript, HTML, & CSS
- Github: github.com/shannacodes/bootstrapSite
- Live Page: rolling-pin-donuts.web.app/

SHANNA LUCERO

Full Stack Web Developer

SOFT SKILLS

- Proactive
- Personable
- Adaptable
- Reliable
- Embraces growth
- Active listener
- Open communication
- Receptive to constructive feedback
- Values camaraderie and collaboration

VOLUNTEER WORK

Maker Space Volunteer

Pleasant Valley School District 2022 - present

Helped kindergarteners and 1st graders learn STEM concepts through a variety of kid-friendly hands-on labs

WORK EXPERIENCE

SR. OCCUPATIONAL THERAPIST / HAND THERAPIST Hand Rehabilitation Specialists

September 2016 - Present

- Assisted in meeting weekly clinical KPI of >200 total patient visits total per week with 85% success rate
- Produced comprehensive data reports and performed in-depth analysis facilitating strategic business decision-making; key focus areas encompassed referral sources, insurance/payor data, account payable/receivable, and detailed expense reports
- Led a team of junior therapists by providing one-onone mentorship sessions and guidance through their professional growth within a culture of open communication, constructive feedback, and support
- Established processes and procedures to enhance the supplies ordering and receiving process using Cloudbased monitoring and tracking
- Deployed marketing tools to boost patient acquisition by developing SEO-centric social media content, crafting engaging blog posts, and conducting targeted webinars for specific niches
- Provided individualized patient care for people across the lifespan with various hand and upper arm injuries

IT IMPLEMENTATION INTERN Alcoa Fastening Systems

June 2008 - June 2009

- Provided end user training on Oracle purchasing processes through classroom-led and one-on-one training sessions
- Prepared technical training documentation, including user instructions and video tutorials
- Developed comprehensive User Acceptance Testing (UAT) test scripts outlining clear instructions and expected results